Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files, 1885-2008 and undated, bulk 1920-1995 RL.00658
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Ford Motor Company, 1911-2007 and undated, 119 boxes
  - Cars and Trucks
    - Trucks--Restricted
      - Ranger
        - Strategic issues, 1996 (Box FM28)
  - Clippings
    - Cars and Trucks
      - Cars (Box FM29)
        - Alternative fuel models, 1966-1983 (Box FM29)
        - Capri, 1969-1981 (Box FM29)
        - Concept cars, 1963-1985 (Box FM29)
        - Cortina, 1967 (Box FM29)
        - Edsel, 1956-1974 (Box FM29)
        - Escort/Lynx, 1975-1986 (Box FM29)
        - EXP/LN7, 1981-1985 (Box FM29)
        - Fairmont, 1977-1982 (Box FM29)
        - Falcon, 1962-1969 (Box FM29)
        - Fiesta, 1976-1978 (Box FM29)
        - Granada, 1972-1982 (Box FM29)
        - LTD/Crown Victoria, 1975-1983 (Box FM29)
        - Maverick/Comet, 1969-1979 (Box FM29)
        - Model T, 1950-1980 (Box FM29)
        - Mustang, 1964-2004, 2 folders (Box FM29)
        - Pinto/Bobcat, 1970-1980 (Box FM29)
        - Sierra, 1982-1987 (Box FM29)
        - Small cars, 1962-1986, 2005 (Box FM29)
        - Taurus/Sable, 1985-1987 (Box FM29)
        - Tempo/Topaz, 1983-1985 (Box FM29)
        - Thunderbird, 1956-1987 (Box FM29)
        - Miscellaneous, 1959-2005, 3 folders (Box FM29)
      - Sport Utility Vehicles
        - Bronco, 1965-1980 (Box FM29)
        - Miscellaneous, 2000 and undated (Box FM29)
      - Tractors and industrial vehicles, 1961-1986 (Box FM29)
      - Trucks
        - Heavy-Duty, 1959-1986 (Box FM29)
        - Medium-Duty, 1962-1985 (Box FM29)
        - Pickups, 1967-1986 (Box FM29)
        - Ranger, 1981-1986 (Box FM29)
        - Miscellaneous, 1959-1984 (Box FM29)
      - Vans
        - Aerostar, 1985-1986 (Box FM29)
        - Miscellaneous, 1969-1985 (Box FM29)
    - Corporate
      - 75th anniversary, 1977-1978 (Box FM30)
      - Advertising
        - Agencies, 1961-1987 (Box FM30)
        - Campaigns, 1956-1985 (Box FM30)
        - Claims, 1960-1986 (Box FM30)
        - Outdoor, 1963-1984 (Box FM30)
        - Print, 1953-1986 (Box FM30)
        - Radio/Television, 1957-1986 (Box FM30)
        - Miscellaneous, 1953-1987 (Box FM30)
      - Executives
        - Bourke, William O., 1970-1980 (Box FM30)
        - Caldwell, Phillip, 1978-1984 (Box FM30)
        - Iacocca, Lee A., 1964-1984 (Box FM30)
        - Knudsen, Semon E., 1968-1969 (Box FM30)
        - Lutz, Robert A., 1974-1986 (Box FM30)
        - Petersen, Donald E., 1979-1986 (Box FM30)
        - Poling, Harold A., 1979-1986 (Box FM30)
        - Miscellaneous, 1953-1987, 3 folders (Box FM30)
      - [Ford 100 Automotive News commemorative edition, 2003: moved to Oversize Box FM-OV1] (Box FM30)
      - Ford family
        - Benson Jr., 1977-1979 (Box FM30)
        - Edsel Jr., 1978-1986 (Box FM30)
        - Henry, 1923-1986 (Box FM30)
        - Henry II, 1946-1986, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box FM30)
        - Henry II (continued), 1946-1986, 3 of 3 folders (Box FM31)
        - William Clay, 1978-1980 (Box FM31)
        - Miscellaneous, 1957-1984 (Box FM31)
      - International operations, 1956-1987, 4 folders (Box FM31)
      - Legal/Regulatory issues, 1957-1985 (Box FM31)
      - Manufacturing/Technical articles, 1959-1987 (Box FM31)
      - Motorsports, 1959-1985 (Box FM31)
      - Price increases, 1976-1986 (Box FM31)
      - Recalls, 1976-1987 (Box FM31)
      - United Auto Workers, 1955-1987 (Box FM31)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1987, 1-2 of 4 folders (Box FM31)
      - Miscellaneous (continued), 1947-1987, 3-4 of 4 folders (Box FM32)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA)
    - Chronological Files
      - 1974-1980, 11 folders (Box FM33)
      - 1980-1983, 9 folders (Box FM34)
      - 1984-1988, 6 folders (Box FM35)
  - Ford/Citibank Credit Card Partnership
    - General, 1992-1994, 2 folders (Box FM36)
    - Advertising plan, circa 1994 (Box FM36)
    - Business Review Board, 1993-1994 (Box FM36)
    - Creativity and media, 1994 (Box FM36)
    - Consumer proposition meeting, 1993 (Box FM36)
    - Dealership posters, 1993 (Box FM36)
    - Drive calendar, 1994 (Box FM36)
    - Focus groups, 1993 (Box FM36)
    - GM credit card program, 1994 (Box FM36)
    - Gold card, 1993 (Box FM36)
    - Gold card storyboard tests, 1993 (Box FM36)
    - Hot Rod spots, 1993-1994 (Box FM36)
    - Making a Name for Yourself in the '90s, pitch by Michael Butler and Jim Van der Eyk, 1988 (Box FM36)
    - Marketing plan, 1994 (Box FM36)
    - Program review, 1994 (Box FM36)
    - Re-Focus on the Potential, report by Carlson Marketing Group, circa 1994 (Box FM36)
    - Status updates, 1993-1994 (Box FM36)
    - Team status meetings, 1993 (Box FM36)
    - Thank You, Inc. proposal, undated (Box FM36)
    - Times Mirror proposal, 1994 (Box FM36)
    - Update summary, 1992 (Box FM36)
    - U.S. Market Hotline, 1993 (Box FM36)
  - Ford/Citibank Credit Card Partnership--Restricted
    - General, 1995 (Box FM37)
    - Bingo card opportunity, 1995 (Box FM37)
    - Brand awareness tracking, 1995 (Box FM37)
    - Confidentiality agreement, 1995 (Box FM37)
    - Dairy Panel research, 1996 (Box FM37)
    - Dealer's Choice proposal, 1995 (Box FM37)
    - Eric Knowlton reader file, 1994-1995 (Box FM37)
  - Ford Today Global Campaign--Restricted
    - General Files
      - Binders--Ford Today, 1995-1996, 6 folders (Box FM38)
      - Binders--Ford Today and Tomorrow, 1995, 2 folders (Box FM38)
      - Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box FM38)
      - Country lists/information, 1997 (Box FM38)
      - Cover sheets and binder spines, 1998 (Box FM39)
      - Global audit, undated (Box FM39)
      - Planning, 1993 (Box FM39)
    - Presentations
      - Ford Regional Brand Development--Asia, 1995 (Box FM39)
      - Ford Today, 1996-1997 and undated, 5 folders (Box FM39)
      - Global Marketing Communications Program, 1997 (Box FM39)
      - World Class Communications Concept, 1996, 3 folders (Box FM39)
      - Worldwide Direct Market Operation, 1997 (Box FM39)
      - Worldwide Export Operations, 1996, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box FM39)
      - Worldwide Export Operations (continued), 1996, 3 of 3 folders (Box FM40)
      - Report by JWT Ford GBU, 1996 (Box FM40)
      - Report--Qualitative Concept Exploration, 1994 (Box FM40)
      - Research, 1997 (Box FM40)
      - Situation analysis, 1995 (Box FM40)
    - International Markets
      - General (Box FM40)
      - Correspondence binder, 1997, 3 folders (Box FM40)
      - Media plans, 1997, 3 folders (Box FM40)
      - Uden, 1996-1997 (Box FM40)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, schedules, etc., 1998 (Box FM40)
    - Argentina (Box FM41)
      - [Press releases, 1999, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV4] (Box FM41)
    - Asia-Pacific
      - General, 1995-1998, 2 folders (Box FM41)
      - Cycle 1 program, 1997 (Box FM41)
      - Cycle 4-11, circa 1998 (Box FM41)
      - Ford Today and environment, undated (Box FM41)
      - Memoranda, 1995-1997, 5 folders (Box FM41)
      - Print advertising, 1997 and undated, 2 folders (Box FM41)
      - Time Magazine Asia, 1997, 2 folders (Box FM41)
    - Australia
      - Ford Today and environment, 1992-1997, 2 folders (Box FM41)
      - Memoranda, 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box FM41)
      - Research Report on a Blueprint for the Future Format and Content of Ford Today, 1996 (Box FM41)
      - Research Report on Advertising Tracking, 1995 (Box FM41)
      - Research Report on the Effectiveness of Ford Today, 1993-1994, 1-5 of 7 folders (Box FM41)
      - Research Report on the Effectiveness of Ford Today (continued), 1993-1994, 6-7 of 7 folders (Box FM42)
      - Talent agreement, 1997 (Box FM42)
    - Egypt
      - Scripts, 1997-1998 (Box FM42)
    - England
      - Presentation, undated (Box FM42)
      - Research from Cairo, 1997 (Box FM42)
      - Screening certificates, 1996 (Box FM42)
      - Scripts, 1996 (Box FM42)
    - Europe
      - Central meetings, 1995, 2 folders (Box FM42)
      - Information packs, 1994-1997, 2 folders (Box FM42)
      - Memoranda, 1995 (Box FM42)
      - Pan-European Ford meeting, 1995 (Box FM42)
    - Germany (Frankfurt)
      - Ford Today episodes, 1997-1998 (Box FM42)
      - Germany/Israel episodes, 1997-1998 (Box FM42)
    - Israel (Box FM43)
      - General, 1996 (Box FM43)
      - Production, 1997 (Box FM43)
      - Scripts, 1997-1998 (Box FM43)
    - Korea
      - Memoranda, 1996, 2 folders (Box FM43)
    - Middle East
      - Topics, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box FM43)
    - Peru
      - Media schedule, 1997 (Box FM43)
    - Russia
      - Episodes, 1997 (Box FM43)
      - Ford Today Russia, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box FM43)
      - Infomercial, 1997 (Box FM43)
      - Media plans, 1996-1997, 5 folders (Box FM43)
      - Qualitative study, 1997 (Box FM43)
      - Russian production, 1997 (Box FM43)
      - Scripts, 1997-1998 (Box FM43)
      - Status report, 1997 (Box FM43)
      - Topics, 1996-1997, 5 folders (Box FM43)
    - Saudia Arabia (Box FM44)
      - Scripts, 1995-1998, 2 folders (Box FM44)
    - Slovenia
      - Scripts, 1998 (Box FM44)
    - Taiwan
      - Effectiveness of Ford Today, 1995 (Box FM44)
    - Venezuela
      - Actualidad Ford, 1997 (Box FM44)
      - Title list, 1997 (Box FM44)
  - Global Anthem Campaign
    - Article, The Making of the Ford Trustmark Global Anthem, by Jill Powell1999 (Box FM45)
    - Articles and clippings, 1999 (Box FM45)
    - Awards and nominations, 2000-2001 (Box FM45)
    - [Book, Global Anthem Hello/Goodbye, undated, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV3] (Box FM45)
    - Charlotte Church, 1999 (Box FM45)
    - Internet promotions (Ford.com), 1999-2001 (Box FM45)
    - Music, Goodbye/Hello, Global Trustmark Anthem (score and notes), undated (Box FM45)
    - Press releases from Argentina, 1999 (Box FM45)
    - Print advertising, 1999 (Box FM45)
    - Television commercials stills, undated (Box FM45)
  - Global Anthem Campaign--Restricted
    - General (objectives, purpose, background), 1998-1999 (Box FM46)
    - Budget, 1999-2004, 2 folders (Box FM46)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box FM46)
    - Creative strategy, 1999 (Box FM46)
    - Hachette Filipacchi presentation, 1999 (Box FM46)
    - Legal, 1999 (Box FM46)
    - Meetings, 1999 (Box FM46)
    - Presentations, 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box FM47)
    - Print proposals, 1999 (Box FM47)
    - Research, 1999 (Box FM47)
    - Talent, 1999-2001 (Box FM47)
    - Talent Releases
      - Argentina, 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box FM47)
      - Australia, 1999-2000 (Box FM47)
    - Talent Releases (continued) (Box FM48)
      - Canada (Vancouver), 1999-2000 (Box FM48)
      - China, 1999-2000, 3 folders (Box FM48)
      - England, 1999-2000 (Box FM48)
      - Germany, 1999-2000 (Box FM48)
    - Talent Releases (continued) (Box FM49)
      - Italy, 1999-2000 (Box FM49)
      - Japan, 1999-2000, 3 folders (Box FM49)
      - Television campaign, 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box FM49)
      - Television commercials--General, 1999, 1 of 3 folders (Box FM49)
      - Television commercials--General (continued), 1999, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box FM50)
      - Television commercials--International, 2004-2005, 2 folders (Box FM50)
      - Time Magazine campaign, 1999-2000 (Box FM50)
      - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box FM50)
  - Global Anthem Campaign--Closed
    - Budget for talent costs, 1999-2000, 3 folders (Box FM51)
  - Global Business Unit (GBU)--Restricted
    - First meeting binder, 2000, 3 folders (Box FM52)
    - GBU Automotive Excellence--Retail Case Studies, 2001 (Box FM52)
    - GBU Conference, 2003 (Box FM52)
    - GBU in Motion, 2003, 2 folders (Box FM52)
    - GBU Passport, 2001 (Box FM52)
    - Global Business Partnership Report, Fourth Quarter 1995, 1996 (Box FM52)
    - Global Business Unit Report, Third Quarter 1995, 1995 (Box FM52)
    - Road Warriors Conference, 2001, 2 folders (Box FM52)
    - [Miscellaneous, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV5] (Box FM52)
  - International
    - General (Box FM53)
      - [Board game, top Marques, undated, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV3] (Box FM53)
      - Ford overseas distributors status report, 1962 (Box FM53)
    - Australia
      - Ford Brand Image Consumer Perceptions, 1991 (Box FM53)
    - Brazil
      - Automotive industry, 1994 (Box FM53)
      - [Print advertising samples, 1990, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV4] (Box FM53)
    - Canada
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box FM53)
    - England
      - Research, 1989 (Box FM53)
    - Europe
      - [Introduction of new Ford farm tractors, 1964, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV4] (Box FM53)
    - Germany
      - 8-Box Segmentation Analysis, 1989 (Box FM53)
      - [Study group proposal, 1979, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV4] (Box FM53)
    - India
      - [Booklet, Winning the World Over, 1996, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV4] (Box FM53)
    - Japan
      - Competitive--BMW 850I, 1989 (Box FM53)
      - To-do lists, 1993 (Box FM53)
    - Mexico
      - U.S. Medium and Heavy Truck Market Overview, 1993 (Box FM53)
    - South Africa
      - [Introduction of Ford Cortina V6, 1973, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV4] (Box FM53)
  - International--Restricted
    - General (Box FM54)
      - Bassett, Ogilvy & Mather, Publicidad, 1996 (Box FM54)
      - Corporate advertising (in Spanish), undated (Box FM54)
      - Ford Profit and Loss by Country, 1995 (Box FM54)
      - Great Car Launch, 1998, 2 folders (Box FM54)
      - KA print campaign, 2002 (Box FM54)
    - Argentina
      - Brand plans, 1997 (Box FM54)
      - Escort case study, 1996 (Box FM54)
      - Explorer launch materials, circa 1997 (Box FM55)
      - F-100 launch, circa 1997 (Box FM55)
      - Fiesta launch, 1996, 2 folders (Box FM55)
      - Guia Ford, 1998 (Box FM55)
      - JWT/Y&R/WCJ partnership presentation, circa 1998, 2 folders (Box FM55)
      - KA launch, 1997 (Box FM55)
      - Strategic plan, 1999 (Box FM55)
    - Asia-Pacific
      - Market development plan, 1996 (Box FM55)
      - Promotional materials, 2005 (Box FM55)
      - Video list, 1999 (Box FM55)
    - Australia (Box FM56)
      - 3 Directions dealer VIP presentation kit, circa 1998 (Box FM56)
      - 3 Years/100,000 km Bumper-to-Bumper Warranty presentation, 1998 (Box FM56)
      - Account Status Book, 1995 (Box FM56)
      - Australian Car Market, 1995, 3 folders (Box FM56)
      - Ford Courier Turbo Diesel presentation, 1999 (Box FM57)
      - Ford Detour Launch Video presentation, 1999 (Box FM57)
      - Explorer, 1998 (Box FM57)
      - Fairlane, 1999 (Box FM57)
      - Falcon Dealer VIP Presentation Kit, circa 1998 (Box FM58)
      - Falcon Ute, 1999, 2 folders (Box FM58)
      - Ford Australia Primary Branding Repositioning, circa 1998 (Box FM58)
      - Laser, 1999 (Box FM58)
      - Live It campaign, 1998, 1 of 3 folders (Box FM58)
      - Live It campaign (continued), 1998, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box FM59)
      - Melbourne Auto Show post analysis, 1999 (Box FM59)
      - Printed materials, 1999 (Box FM59)
      - Team RS, 2004 (Box FM59)
    - Bulgaria (Box FM60)
      - Advertising market, 1996 (Box FM60)
    - Canada
      - Goldfarb report, The Automotive Marketplace in Canada, 2002 (Box FM60)
      - Presentation, circa 2001, 3 folders (Box FM60)
    - Caribbean/Central America
      - Primary Brand Positioning Campaign, 2000 (Box FM60)
    - Chile
      - List of television commercials, 1997 (Box FM60)
      - Parts and service study, 1996 (Box FM60)
    - England (Box FM61)
      - B256/256 (Fiesta) Positioning and Communications, 2001 (Box FM61)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box FM61)
      - Middle East review, 1996, 2 folders (Box FM61)
      - Proposal for partnership with Stewart Grand Prix, 1995 (Box FM61)
      - Scripts and storyboards, 2002 (Box FM61)
    - Europe (Box FM62)
      - CD132 (Mondeo) strategy, 2000 (Box FM62)
      - Communications brief, V184/5 (Transit) launch, 2000 (Box FM62)
      - European Campaign for a Multi-National Company: Ford Corporate Image Improvement Program, 1980s (Box FM62)
      - Fiesta B256 launch, 2002 (Box FM62)
      - Geneva Auto Show press information, 1997 (Box FM62)
      - KA brand strategy, 1996 (Box FM62)
      - KA launch, 1996 (Box FM62)
      - Mondeo positioning, 2000 (Box FM62)
      - New Fiesta, 1996, 2 folders (Box FM62)
      - Puma, 1997 (Box FM62)
    - Germany
      - Aktuell case study, 1997 (Box FM62)
      - KA launch, 1996 (Box FM63)
      - Mondeo, 2001 (Box FM63)
    - India
      - Corporate advertising, 1996 (Box FM63)
    - Israel
      - Focus groups, 1997 (Box FM63)
      - Printed materials, 1997 (Box FM63)
    - Japan
      - Account Book, 1997 (Box FM63)
      - Account Status Book, 1995, 2 folders (Box FM63)
      - Competitive--Nissan Cube, 1998 (Box FM63)
      - Mondeo launch, 1998, 1 folders (Box FM63)
      - Mondeo launch (continued), 1998, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box FM64)
      - Mondeo survey report, 1995 (Box FM64)
    - Latin America
      - Fiesta, 2002 (Box FM64)
      - Fiesta--Amazon Project, 2002 (Box FM64)
      - Mondeo launch, circa 1998 (Box FM64)
      - Sales analysis, 1997 (Box FM65)
    - Mexico
      - 4 Ruedas, 1996 (Box FM65)
      - Fiesta launch, 1998 (Box FM65)
      - Ford distribution, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box FM65)
    - New Zealand
      - Printed materials, 2000 (Box FM65)
    - Peru
      - Ranger pre-test, 1996 (Box FM65)
      - Ranger Ride-and-Drive and launch, 1997 (Box FM65)
    - Romania
      - Car market overview, circa 1996 (Box FM65)
    - Russia
      - Ford for Russia, 1995, 1997, 2 folders (Box FM65)
      - Mondeo, 2001 (Box FM65)
      - Moscow Auto Show, 1996 (Box FM65)
      - Voice of the Automotive Customer, 1996 (Box FM65)
    - Taiwan (Box FM66)
      - Festiva, 1998 (Box FM66)
      - Grand Festiva launch, 1998, 2 folders (Box FM66)
      - Liata launch, 1998 (Box FM66)
      - Lio Ho Advertising Review, circa 1995 (Box FM66)
      - Mondeo launch, 1998 (Box FM66)
      - Printed materials, 1995 (Box FM66)
      - Pronto launch, 1998 (Box FM66)
      - Retail programs, 1998 (Box FM66)
      - Scorpio/Taurus launch, 1998 (Box FM66)
    - Turkey
      - [Ford history, 1997, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV4] (Box FM66)
      - Mondeo, 1996 (Box FM66)
    - United Arab Emirates
      - Crown Victoria, 1997 (Box FM66)
      - Explorer/Taurus/Tracer, 1997 (Box FM66)
      - Habits and attitude study, 1993 (Box FM66)
  - Legal
    - Trademarks of Ford Motor Company, 1959 and undated, 2 folders (Box FM67)
  - Legal--Restricted
    - Corporate Identification Trustmark Standards, 1998 (Box FM68)
    - Ford/Conde Nast CD-ROM promotion, 1997, 4 folders (Box FM68)
    - Ford Corporate Trademark Guidelines, circa 2002 (Box FM68)
    - Legal Claims Book, 1998-2002, 4 folders (Box FM68)
    - Legal Claims Manual, 2000 (Box FM68)
  - Motorsports
    - Advertising, 1986-1990, 2 folders (Box FM67)
    - Inside the Oval, 2006 (Box FM67)
    - Return to Glory (Autoweek special advertising section), 1992 (Box FM67)
    - Slogan awareness study (Winona Market Research Bureau), 1990 (Box FM67)
  - Motorsports--Restricted
    - General, 1997-2000 and undated, 2 folders (Box FM69)
    - Global Business Unit, Motor 'Eyes' conference, 1999 (Box FM69)
    - Global Motorsports Strategy Review, 1998 (Box FM69)
    - NHRA Ford Racing Fan Nationals, 2002 (Box FM69)
    - [Sign, undated: moved to Oversize Box FM-OV2] (Box FM69)
    - Television, 1999 (Box FM69)
  - Photographs
    - Cars and Trucks
      - 600 Series, 1964 (Box FM70)
      - 700 Series, 1960s-1970s, 2 folders (Box FM70)
      - 800 Series, 1970s, 4 folders (Box FM70)
      - 850 Series, 1965-1968, 2 folders (Box FM70)
      - 8000 Custom Cab, circa 1970 (Box FM70)
      - 9000 Series, 1970s, 3 folders (Box FM70)
      - Aerostar, 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box FM70)
      - American Road camper, 1974, 2 folders (Box FM70)
      - B-750 school bus, undated (Box FM70)
      - B-Series, 1973-1979, 2 folders (Box FM70)
      - Base model coupe, 1959 (Box FM70)
      - Bronco, 1966-1982 and undated, 1-53 of 54 folders: 1 folder moved to Oversize Box FM-OV2 (Box FM70)
      - Bronco II, 1983-1985 and undated, 15 folders (Box FM71)
      - C-600, 1958, 1973, 2 folders (Box FM71)
      - C-750, 1965, 1971, 2 folders (Box FM71)
      - C-850, 1968 (Box FM71)
      - C-8000, undated (Box FM71)
      - C-Series, 1965 (Box FM71)
      - Cement mixer, 1961 (Box FM71)
      - Club Wagon, 1969-1983, 9 folders (Box FM71)
      - Cobra, 1962 (Box FM71)
      - Condor II motor home, undated (Box FM71)
      - Contour, 1996-1999, 2 folders (Box FM71)
      - Convertible Coupe, 1939 (Box FM71)
      - Country Sedan, 1952, 1959, 5 folders (Box FM71)
      - Country Squire, 1949-1971, 7 folders (Box FM71)
      - Courier, 1972-1983 and undated, 15 folders (Box FM71)
      - Crestline, 1952-1954, 7 folders (Box FM71)
      - Crestliner, 1950-1951, 2 folders (Box FM71)
      - Crown Victoria, 1980s-1990s, 3 folders (Box FM71)
      - Cruising Van, undated (Box FM71)
      - CT-850, 1965 (Box FM71)
      - Custom, 1951, 1959, 4 folders (Box FM71)
      - Customline, 1952-1954, 6 folders (Box FM72)
      - Deluxe, 1948, 1951, 2 folders (Box FM72)
      - Econoline van, 1961-1985, 49 folders (Box FM72)
      - Ecostar, 1993 (Box FM72)
      - Escort, 1995-1998 and undated, 6 folders (Box FM72)
      - Expedition, 1990s and undated, 2 folders (Box FM72)
      - Explorer, 1972-1996 and undated, 4 folders (Box FM72)
      - F-100, 1957, 9 folders (Box FM72)
      - F-100 (continued), 1961-1984 and undated, 77 folders (Box FM73)
      - F-150, 1976-1999 and undated, 28 folders (Box FM74)
      - F-250, 1964-1980s and undated, 18 folders (Box FM74)
      - F-350, 1957-1973, 14 folders (Box FM74)
      - F-350 (continued), 1980s-1990s and undated, 9 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-500, 1957, 7 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-600, 1961-1970s and undated, 19 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-600/750, 1971, 2 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-600/800, 1954-1955 (Box FM75)
      - F-650 (?), 1990s (Box FM75)
      - F-700, 1965-1973, 4 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-750, 1967-1973, 12 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-800, 1968, 4 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-850, 1965, 1969, 3 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-880, 1973 (Box FM75)
      - F-1000, 1963 and undated, 2 folders (Box FM75)
      - F-8000, undated (Box FM75)
      - F-Series, 1967-1985 and undated, 1-13 of 14 folders: 1 folder moved to Oversize Box FM-OV2 (Box FM75)
      - Fairlane, 1958-1970, 16 folders (Box FM76)
      - Falcon, 1960-1963, 4 folders (Box FM76)
      - Fiesta, undated (Box FM76)
      - Fire trucks, 1955-1961 and undated, 41 folders (Box FM76)
      - Galaxie, 1959, 8 folders (Box FM76)
      - German commercial vehicles, 1990s (Box FM76)
      - Granada, undated (Box FM76)
      - H-750 sleeper cab, 1965 (Box FM77)
      - H-950, 1962-1965, 6 folders (Box FM77)
      - H-1000, 1963 and undated, 4 folders (Box FM77)
      - L-800, 1961 (Box FM77)
      - L-9000, 1970, 2 folders (Box FM77)
      - Lincoln-Mercury, multiple models, 1990s (Box FM77)
      - Louisville Series, 1990s, 6 folders (Box FM77)
      - LTD, 1970-1972 (Box FM77)
      - Mainline, 1952-1953, 2 folders (Box FM77)
      - Maverick, 1971 (Box FM77)
      - Mercury van, undated (Box FM77)
      - [Model A roadster, circa 1930, moved to Oversize Box FM-OV5] (Box FM77)
      - Model A station wagon, 1929 (Box FM77)
      - Model F, circa 1905 (Box FM77)
      - Model T, 1914 (Box FM77)
      - Multiple models, 1965-1997, 6 folders (Box FM77)
      - Mustang, 1964-1990s, 4 folders (Box FM77)
      - N-600, 1963, 1970, 5 folders (Box FM77)
      - N-700, 1968, 3 folders (Box FM77)
      - N-750, 1963, 2 folders (Box FM77)
      - N-800, 1970 (Box FM77)
      - N-950-D, 1963-1969, 6 folders (Box FM77)
      - N-1000, 1963 (Box FM77)
      - N-6000, 1963, 1967, 3 folders (Box FM77)
      - N-8000, 1970, 4 folders (Box FM77)
      - N-9000, undated, 3 folders (Box FM77)
      - N-Series, 1961-1968 and undated, 8 folders (Box FM77)